{
    "response_code": 0,
    "results": [
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "category": "Reading and Writing",
            "question": "Volunteering, or giving time for a community service for free, is a valuable form of civic engagement because helping in a community is also good for society as a whole. In a survey of youths in the United States, most young people said that they believe volunteering is a way to help people on an individual level. Meanwhile, only 6% of the youths said that they think volunteering is a way to help fix problems in society overall. These replies suggest that ______",
            "correct_answer": "volunteering may be even more helpful than many young people think it is.",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "many young people think they can volunteer only within their own communities.",
                "volunteering can help society overall more than it can help individual people.",
                "many young people may not know how to find ways to volunteer their time."
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "category": "Reading and Writing",
            "question": "Etched into Peru’s Nazca Desert are line drawings so large that they can only be fully seen from high above. Archaeologists have known of the lines since the 1920s, when a researcher spotted some from a nearby foothill, and they have been studying the markings ever since. ______ archaeologists’ efforts are aided by drones that capture high-resolution aerial photographs of the lines.",
            "correct_answer": "Currently,",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "In comparison,",
                "Still,",
                "However"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "category": "Reading and Writing",
            "question": "In assessing the films of Japanese director Akira Kurosawa, ______ have missed his equally deep engagement with Japanese artistic traditions such as Noh theater.",
            "correct_answer": "many critics have focused on Kurosawa’s use of Western literary sources but",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Kurosawa’s use of Western literary sources has been the focus of many critics, who",
                "there are many critics who have focused on Kurosawa’s use of Western literary sources, but they",
                "the focus of many critics has been on Kurosawa’s use of Western literary sources; they"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "category": "Reading and Writing",
            "question": "During a 2014 archaeological dig in Spain, Vicente Lull and his team uncovered the skeleton of a woman from El Algar, an Early Bronze Age society, buried with valuable objects signaling a high position of power. This finding may persuade researchers who have argued that Bronze Age societies were ruled by men to ______ that women may have also held leadership roles.",
            "correct_answer": "concede",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "waive",
                "refute",
                "require"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "category": "Reading and Writing",
            "question": "Seneca sculptor Marie Watt’s blanket art comes in a range of shapes and sizes. In 2004, Watt sewed strips of blankets together to craft a 10-by-13-inch ______ in 2014, she arranged folded blankets into two large stacks and then cast them in bronze, creating two curving 18-foot-tall blue-bronze pillars.",
            "correct_answer": "sampler;",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "sampler later,",
                "sampler,",
                "sampler, later,"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "category": "Reading and Writing",
            "question": "The city of Pompeii, which was buried in ash following the eruption of Mount Vesuvius in 79 CE, continues to be studied by archaeologists. Unfortunately, as ______ attest, archaeological excavations have disrupted ash deposits at the site, causing valuable information about the eruption to be lost.",
            "correct_answer": "researchers Roberto Scandone and Christopher Kilburn",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "researchers, Roberto Scandone and Christopher Kilburn,",
                "researchers, Roberto Scandone and Christopher Kilburn",
                "researchers Roberto Scandone, and Christopher Kilburn"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "category": "Reading and Writing",
            "question": "As Mexico’s first president from an Indigenous community, Benito Juarez became one of the most ______ figures in his country’s history: among the many significant accomplishments of his long tenure in office (1858–1872), Juarez consolidated the authority of the national government and advanced the rights of Indigenous peoples.",
            "correct_answer": "important",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "unpredictable",
                "secretive",
                "ordinary"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "category": "Reading and Writing",
            "question": "Atoms in a synchrotron, a type of circular particle accelerator, travel faster and faster until they ______ a desired energy level, at which point they are diverted to collide with a target, smashing the atoms.",
            "correct_answer": "reach",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "will reach",
                "had reached",
                "are reaching"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "category": "Reading and Writing",
            "question": "In winter, the diets of Japanese macaques, also known as snow monkeys, are influenced more by food availability than by food preference. Although the monkeys prefer to eat vegetation and land-dwelling invertebrates, those food sources may become unavailable because of extensive snow and ice cover, ______ the monkeys to hunt for marine animals in any streams that have not frozen over.",
            "correct_answer": "forcing",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "forces",
                "to force",
                "forced"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "category": "Reading and Writing",
            "question": "Literary agents estimate that more than half of all nonfiction books credited to a celebrity or other public figure are in fact written by ghostwriters, professional authors who are paid to write other ______ but whose names never appear on book covers.",
            "correct_answer": "people’s stories",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "peoples story’s",
                "peoples stories",
                "people’s story’s"
            ]
        }
    ]
}
